Hello friends. I'm Steve Mona. I'm Pete McDaniel. Craig Kirby here. I'm DeBert Cook, and I'm honored to be part of the Celebrate 120 Advisory Committee.
2026 represents a historical milestone in Gulf's history. We are coming together to recognize two historic anniversaries.
Clearview Golf Course, known as America's Course, will celebrate its 80th year of continuous operation.
The National Black Golf Hall of Fame, founded by Harold Donovan, celebrates its 40th anniversary.
These two organizations have come together collectively to celebrate this historical moment.
120 years celebrating Gulf's Black history.
We invite you to join us on Friday and Saturday, October 2nd and 3rd,
at the historic Clearview Golf Course in East Canton, Ohio.
120 years celebrating Gulf's Black history.
We are commemorating Celebration 120.
We look forward to seeing you there. I look forward to seeing you there. I'll be there. I want you. Peace.